<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Frequently Asked Questions | BrainHack Global</title>
    <link>/faq/</link>
      <atom:link href="/faq/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Frequently Asked Questions</description>
    <generator>Source Themes Academic (https://sourcethemes.com/academic/)</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>© BrainHack Global 2020</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sun, 09 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>/images/icon_hu0b7a4cb9992c9ac0e91bd28ffd38dd00_9727_512x512_fill_lanczos_center_2.png</url>
      <title>Frequently Asked Questions</title>
      <link>/faq/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>Section 1 - General FAQ</title>
      <link>/faq/general/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/faq/general/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div class=&#34;faq-section-section&#34;&gt;&lt;h3&gt;General&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;accordion&#34; id=&#34;faq&#34;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;card&#34;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;card-header collapsed&#34; data-toggle=&#34;collapse&#34; data-target=&#34;#collapse-0-0&#34; aria-expanded=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&lt;p&gt;What is Brainhack Global? What is the difference between global and local event sites?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div id=&#34;collapse-0-0&#34; class=&#34;collapse&#34; data-parent=&#34;#faq&#34; style=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;card-body&#34;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Brainhack Global (BHG) is an umbrella term for all the hacking events run all around the world and for the central organizing committee which coordinates and helps in the planning and organization of the local events all around the world. Brainhack Global is constituted by a volunteer team of researchers from a variety of research institutions. The team is in charge of designing the proceedings of Brainhack Global as well as maintaining the Brainhack Global materials, websites, and social accounts. Brainhack Global does not run a separate hacking event at any specific location or time but shares the information, materials, and broadcasts from all local event sites during the defined event period.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Local event sites refer to the local Brainhack events, where a group of researchers from local institutes comes together and runs hacking events for any period of time. These local events are entirely independent in designing their program and event schedule, tutorial materials, recruiting their attendees and speakers, and finding their funding and venues. The events might include educational tutorials, unconferences, hacking, and social events. The Brainhack Global team helps the local event sites by providing them with all the necessary guidelines and tools that would facilitate the organization of the local event sites and also helps them with the announcement of their event all around the world via its website and social accounts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;card&#34;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;card-header&#34; data-toggle=&#34;collapse&#34; data-target=&#34;#collapse-0-1&#34;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Is Brainhack Global run by an institute / company / individuals?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div id=&#34;collapse-0-1&#34; class=&#34;collapse&#34; data-parent=&#34;#faq&#34;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;card-body&#34;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Brainhack Global is a series of hacking events that aims to celebrate the application of open science practices in neuroscience research. At the same time, it seeks to foster collaboration among researchers from a variety of career levels and backgrounds. Brainhack Global provides a collective and collaborative unique frame that includes hacking, educational tutorials, unconference events, and networking opportunities between the attendees and event sites. The organization is run voluntarily by a team of individuals (usually graduate students, post-docs, researchers, and professors) that are involved in research in neurosciences at various institutions all around the world.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;card&#34;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;card-header&#34; data-toggle=&#34;collapse&#34; data-target=&#34;#collapse-0-2&#34;&gt;&lt;p&gt;May I be involved with the Brainhack Global team?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div id=&#34;collapse-0-2&#34; class=&#34;collapse&#34; data-parent=&#34;#faq&#34;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;card-body&#34;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Any help you would like to offer is more than welcome! You may be part of Brainhack Global by either joining the Brainhack Global team or by organizing a local event for the upcoming year. Each year, the Brainhack Global team announces to collect interests for the volunteering teams via its own Mattermost channel or via email lists. If you would like to help out, please look out for those announcements and contact us.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;card&#34;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;card-header&#34; data-toggle=&#34;collapse&#34; data-target=&#34;#collapse-0-3&#34;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Is there a limit on the number of local events held each year?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div id=&#34;collapse-0-3&#34; class=&#34;collapse&#34; data-parent=&#34;#faq&#34;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;card-body&#34;&gt;&lt;p&gt;No. We support and encourage as much participation as possible from all around the world to celebrate and disseminate the open science processes and practices.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;card&#34;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;card-header&#34; data-toggle=&#34;collapse&#34; data-target=&#34;#collapse-0-4&#34;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Is there any funding available by Brainhack Global to the local event sites or attendees?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div id=&#34;collapse-0-4&#34; class=&#34;collapse&#34; data-parent=&#34;#faq&#34;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;card-body&#34;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Brainhack Global is a voluntarily run organization, which is not funded or supported by any global/local agency, company, or institute. Therefore, Brainhack Global does not have any resources to support either the hosting event sites or the attendees financially. It is the responsibility of the hosting event sites’ local organizing committee to secure funding both for hosting the event and, if possible, for providing travel awards to a select few attendees.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;card&#34;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;card-header&#34; data-toggle=&#34;collapse&#34; data-target=&#34;#collapse-0-5&#34;&gt;&lt;p&gt;How can we contact the Brainhack Global team?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div id=&#34;collapse-0-5&#34; class=&#34;collapse&#34; data-parent=&#34;#faq&#34;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;card-body&#34;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Please send an email to brainhackorg@gmail.com with a brief description of your event’s plan, including details about the contact point(s)/organizer(s) (i.e., their email(s) and affiliation lab(s)/institution(s)), the event location (city, country, event site/institute), the event dates, the event website (if available), the number of attendees you plan to host, and whether you will broadcast any tutorials. As soon as the team receives your email, you will be provided with a welcoming pack that includes all the necessary guidance and information for you to start planning the event.  &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;card&#34;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;card-header&#34; data-toggle=&#34;collapse&#34; data-target=&#34;#collapse-0-6&#34;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Where can I see the previous years’ events?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div id=&#34;collapse-0-6&#34; class=&#34;collapse&#34; data-parent=&#34;#faq&#34;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;card-body&#34;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://brainhack.org&#34;&gt;Here&lt;/a&gt; you can find all the previous years’ event sites, contact points, and the link to their websites.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;card&#34;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;card-header&#34; data-toggle=&#34;collapse&#34; data-target=&#34;#collapse-0-7&#34;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Where can I see the current event locations?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div id=&#34;collapse-0-7&#34; class=&#34;collapse&#34; data-parent=&#34;#faq&#34;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;card-body&#34;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://brainhack.org/global2019/locations&#34;&gt;Here&lt;/a&gt; you can find updated information about all the confirmed event sites for a this year’s Brainhack Global event.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;card&#34;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;card-header&#34; data-toggle=&#34;collapse&#34; data-target=&#34;#collapse-0-8&#34;&gt;&lt;p&gt;How can I watch online streaming tutorials?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div id=&#34;collapse-0-8&#34; class=&#34;collapse&#34; data-parent=&#34;#faq&#34;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;card-body&#34;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://calendar.google.com/calendar?cid=ODJtZnVkNHNuZWVhYTk5MWI1cXB1MXJtNTRAZ3JvdXAuY2FsZW5kYXIuZ29vZ2xlLmNvbQ&#34;&gt;Here&lt;/a&gt; you can find a schedule of all the local event sites and access their broadcasts in the proposed program. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;card&#34;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;card-header&#34; data-toggle=&#34;collapse&#34; data-target=&#34;#collapse-0-9&#34;&gt;&lt;p&gt;May I use the logo of Brainhack Global in my presentations/materials? Where can I find the logo?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div id=&#34;collapse-0-9&#34; class=&#34;collapse&#34; data-parent=&#34;#faq&#34;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;card-body&#34;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yes, you can use the Brainhack logo in your presentations and materials. When you use educational and informational materials, please do not forget to cite the materials’ community/developer(s). &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/brainhackorg/pr-material&#34;&gt;Here&lt;/a&gt; you can download the logo and other materials of Brainhack Global.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;card&#34;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;card-header&#34; data-toggle=&#34;collapse&#34; data-target=&#34;#collapse-0-10&#34;&gt;&lt;p&gt;What are the main social accounts of Brainhack Global?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div id=&#34;collapse-0-10&#34; class=&#34;collapse&#34; data-parent=&#34;#faq&#34;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;card-body&#34;&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Website: &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.brainhack.org/global2019&#34;&gt;http://www.brainhack.org/global2019&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Twitter: &lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/brainhackorg?lang=en-gb&#34;&gt;https://twitter.com/brainhackorg?lang=en-gb&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mattermost: #brainhack-global-2019&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Github: &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/brainhack101&#34;&gt;https://github.com/brainhack101&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;hr class=&#34;d-none d-lg-block mb-0 ml-0&#34;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Section 2 - How to set up your virtual setup</title>
      <link>/faq/hosts/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/faq/hosts/</guid>
      <description>


</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
