<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Local Brainhacks | Brainhack Global 2020</title><link>https://www.brainhack.org/global2020/events/</link><atom:link href="https://www.brainhack.org/global2020/events/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><description>Local Brainhacks</description><generator>Wowchemy (https://wowchemy.com)</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>© Brainhack Global 2020</copyright><image><url>https://www.brainhack.org/global2020/images/icon_hu405768a2e56dba1817ce36477148a60d_2978_512x512_fill_lanczos_center_2.png</url><title>Local Brainhacks</title><link>https://www.brainhack.org/global2020/events/</link></image><item><title>Brainhack Beijing &amp; Nanning</title><link>https://www.brainhack.org/global2020/events/nanning-beijing/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Dec 2020 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.brainhack.org/global2020/events/nanning-beijing/</guid><description>&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://brainhack.live/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Brainhack 2020 Beijing &amp;amp; Nanning&lt;/a> will focus its events on the translational applications of the brain growth charts.
We are thus inviting all the researchers to participate this event and practice the open science. As a basic resource,
the normative data of the brain development across school age will be opened to all the participants who submit a relevant project.
This is a one-week hack event including sessions for education course, project team building and summarizing report.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Brainhack New York</title><link>https://www.brainhack.org/global2020/events/newyork/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Dec 2020 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.brainhack.org/global2020/events/newyork/</guid><description>&lt;p>NY will be a fully virtual event perfect for first-time hackers, with tutorials and guest lectures focused on the development of skills to tackle a variety of computational neuroscience problems. Over the course of two days, you will also be able to participate
in hands-on projects within the Tri-I/Cornell community and beyond.
For the schedule of the event please see the &lt;a href="https://brainhack-ny.github.io/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Brainhack New York website&lt;/a>.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Brainhack Princeton</title><link>https://www.brainhack.org/global2020/events/princeton/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Dec 2020 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.brainhack.org/global2020/events/princeton/</guid><description>&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://brainhack-princeton.github.io/2020/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Brainhack Princeton&lt;/a> will (virtually) bring together researchers to collaborate on projects
aimed at improving open and reproducible neuroscience. Over the course of three days, participants will pitch projects and work together on
these projects (e.g. contributing content to the Princeton Handbook for &lt;a href="https://brainhack-princeton.github.io/handbook/index.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Reproducible Neuroscience&lt;/a>).
There will also be tutorials to introduce tools and resources that can be used to facilitate best open science practices in your own work.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>BrainHack Marseille</title><link>https://www.brainhack.org/global2020/events/marseille/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Dec 2020 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.brainhack.org/global2020/events/marseille/</guid><description>&lt;p>Second edition of Brainhack Marseille&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>BrainHack Western &amp; BrainHack Toronto</title><link>https://www.brainhack.org/global2020/events/western_ontario/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Dec 2020 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.brainhack.org/global2020/events/western_ontario/</guid><description>&lt;p>Our first virtual &lt;a href="https://brainhackto.github.io/global-ON-2020/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">BrainHack Global - Ontario&lt;/a> co-hosted by BrainHack Western and BrainHack Toronto.
Join us on December 2nd to 4th over Chrowdcast for a completely free event focused on neuroscience and the promotion of open-source resources in an
accessible way across disciplines and experience levels including hacking, education, panels, and networking. Even though we will be physically distant,
there will be the possibility to come together and socialize on the Brainhack Ontario GatherTown platform. We will be using the platform to host exciting
social activities throughout the event. Stay tuned for the social activities program!&lt;/p>
&lt;iframe src="https://calendar.google.com/calendar/embed?height=600&amp;wkst=1&amp;bgcolor=%23616161&amp;ctz=America%2FToronto&amp;src=MHRybmNkb2ozYWMzcnNhdm1tOXM1ODBuNmNAZ3JvdXAuY2FsZW5kYXIuZ29vZ2xlLmNvbQ&amp;src=ODJtZnVkNHNuZWVhYTk5MWI1cXB1MXJtNTRAZ3JvdXAuY2FsZW5kYXIuZ29vZ2xlLmNvbQ&amp;src=bmlsZWFybi5ldmVudHNAZ21haWwuY29t&amp;color=%23E4C441&amp;color=%23E67C73&amp;color=%23F6BF26&amp;mode=AGENDA&amp;showNav=0&amp;showTitle=0&amp;showTabs=0&amp;showDate=0&amp;showPrint=0" style="border:solid 1px #777" width="800" height="600" frameborder="0" scrolling="no">&lt;/iframe></description></item><item><title>Brainhack Marburg</title><link>https://www.brainhack.org/global2020/events/marburg/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Nov 2020 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.brainhack.org/global2020/events/marburg/</guid><description>&lt;p>Brainhack is a unique event format that convenes researchers from across the globe and a myriad of disciplines to work together on innovative projects related to neuroscience. Brainhack is a platform where researchers from all educational/professional levels (from undergrad students to professors) work together and participate in open collaboration. Regional Brainhack events keep the momentum going throughout the year.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>In 2020, a local Brainhack event is being organized from researchers of the Philipps-University Marburg, collaborating interdisciplinary (mainly, departments of psychology, german language and literature and medicine). 2020 being 2020, this year’s Brainhack will be held 100% virtual, which makes it possible to participate and collaborate from anywhere on earth.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>The Marburg Brainhack 2020 will focus on educational activities, basing the core values of the Brainhack global community: the application of open, accessible, and transparent science practices (“open science”). We will provide talks and workshops on methods and are looking forward to an exciting exchange of knowledge and ideas. Given the complexity of the field with rapidly emerging approaches and tools to learn and put in practice, we hope that our local Brainhack event contributes to create an organic environment to initiate and encourage quick adoption of these new approaches.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>In addition to the educational activities, participants are welcome to initiate projects to work and collaborate together with other researchers. No requirements exist on what constitutes a valid project. Project proposals could constitute a vague idea on a given topic of interest or a fully developed plan. Intensive project involvement contributes to participants’ skills development, so igniting a project without polished outcomes is common and completely accepted.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>We want to enable researchers with children to completely participate in the Brainhack Marburg. That is why we are particularly pleased to be able to pay for your private child care during the Brainhack, due to the fantastic funding of the UMR vernetzt programme of the Philipps-University Marburg.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Brainhack Pittsburgh</title><link>https://www.brainhack.org/global2020/events/pittsburgh/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Nov 2020 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.brainhack.org/global2020/events/pittsburgh/</guid><description>&lt;p>&lt;a href="openmindslab.com">The Open MINDS Lab&lt;/a>) @ Pitt organizes an amazing and week long Pittsburgh BrianHack event which includes
exciting talks and tutorials on machine learning, deconfounding and tutorials on HPC!
Join our event by filling our
&lt;a href="https://docs.google.com/forms/d/e/1FAIpQLSeA0jMyn3OU_x_ezRR7-eaoxV6YvehpbEAD3V5PZoeWD7zlsw/viewform?usp=send_form" target="_blank" rel="noopener">registration form&lt;/a>&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Brainhack DC</title><link>https://www.brainhack.org/global2020/events/dc/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Nov 2020 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.brainhack.org/global2020/events/dc/</guid><description>&lt;p>Brainhack DC will take place online this year! Over two days, you will also be able to participate in hands-on projects and tutorials focused on developing skills to tackle a variety of problems in neuroscience problems. For the event schedule, please see the Brainhack DC website.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Brainhack Donostia</title><link>https://www.brainhack.org/global2020/events/donostia/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Nov 2020 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.brainhack.org/global2020/events/donostia/</guid><description>&lt;p>Despite the challenges we have faced and continue to work through in 2020, this year, Brainhack Donostia is going to be bigger and better than before! With our new online format, you will have access to workshops, invited talks, and hands-on projects in four main areas of interest: functional magnetic resonance imaging (fMRI), magnetoencephalography (MEG), diffusion imaging (DTI), and Open Science. A gender-balanced board of researchers from BCBL is currently building a five-day workshop composed of talks, tutorials, and project development sessions. &lt;a href="https://brainhack-donostia.github.io" target="_blank" rel="noopener">[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/a> Find out more on their &lt;a href="https://brainhack-donostia.github.io" target="_blank" rel="noopener">website&lt;/a>.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Here&amp;rsquo;s the calendar for this event.&lt;/p>
&lt;iframe src="https://calendar.google.com/calendar/embed?height=1000&amp;amp;wkst=2&amp;amp;bgcolor=%234a578e&amp;amp;src=YmhnLWRvbm9zdGlhQGJjYmwuZXU&amp;amp;color=%23039BE5&amp;amp;title=Brainhack%20Donostia%202020&amp;amp;mode=AGENDA&amp;amp;showTabs=0&amp;amp;showCalendars=0&amp;amp;showPrint=0&amp;amp;tab=mc&amp;amp;mode=week&amp;amp;dates=20201109/20201115&amp;amp;ctz=America/New_York" style="border:solid 1px #777" scrolling="no" width="100%" height="800" frameborder="0">&lt;/iframe></description></item></channel></rss>